Bishnu Thapa

Date of birth: 05/08/1998

Gender: Male

Email address: bishnuthapa1820@gmail.com

Contact number: +977 9806131392 Address: Pokhara, 33700 (Nepal)

Portfolio link: http://bishnuthapa.com

About Me

Experience and creative Front-End Developer with +1.5 years' background in web development. Highly motivated BIT graduate with a good knowledge and experience in front-end web design and development. Passionate about building responsive web design using various frameworks.

Experiences

1) Position: React Developer [Oct 2021 - Current]

Company: **Black Tech**Address: Pokhara, Kaski

Country: Nepal

Link: https://www.blacktech.com.np

Job description: Building responsive web applications for the company's in-house projects

2) Position: Front End Developer [Jan 2021 - Sep 2021]

Company: **Decube IT Solution**

Address: Pokhara, Kaski

Country: Nepal

Link: https://www.facebook.com/dcubeitsolutionpvtltd

Job description: Building responsive web applications using various front-end frameworks

Education

BSc (Hons) in computing: BIT [Jan 2018 - Jun 2021]

College: Informatics College Pokhara

Address: Pokhara, Kaski

Skills

- JavaScript
- React js
- Next js
- Redux
- React Query
- TypeScript
- Tailwind CSS
- Bootstrap
- Reactstrap

Extra Skills

- Python
- Machine Learning (ML) and Deep Learning
- FastAPI
- Django and Django Rest Framework (DRF)

Works References

- https://app.restrox.co/Restrox (Blaktech)
- https://www.booklifter.com/ (Blacktech)
- https://acc.dcubeitsolution.com (DCUBE IT Solution)